<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Practice2</string>
    <string name="show_course_details">Show Course Details</string>
    <string name="description_888">This course focuses on the fundamental design and development of mobile applications and services. The goal of this course is to explore and discuss approaches to the design and development of mobile client-side applications, which can fully leverage a variety of enterprise information systems to meet the needs of business mobility on both the service provider and the customer sides.</string>
    <string name="description_879">This course will focus on the design of computer-based, machine vision systems.  We\'ll discover how to select appropriate algorithms and incorporate best practices.  You will have the opportunity to practice various techniques used in machine vision, such as image representation and structuring, feature extraction and segmentation, information extraction, filtering, and analysis.</string>
    <string name="description_837">SWENG 837 is a three (3) credit course that discusses best practices in the requirements, analysis, and design of large software systems including the Unified Modeling language and the Unified Process.</string>
    <string name="description_505">Over the next seven weeks we will explore the discipline of project management as it relates to engineering and high-technology projects and personnel. Throughout the course, a few topics will highlight the relationship to agile, citing the Project Management Institute (PMI) best practices for that topic.  </string>
    <string name="description_581">SWENG 581 provides a rigorous formal framework and practical information on the testing of software throughout its life cycle.</string>
    <string name="description_861">This course is all about programming and you will learn through the course lessons, exercises, and assignments various programming technologies.</string>
    <string name="description_586">SWENG 586 is a three (3) credit course that explores theory and applications of requirements elicitation, analysis, modeling, validation, testing, and writing for hardware and software systems. </string>
    <string name="description_561">Over the next seven weeks, we will explore practical approaches to discovering, exploiting, and mitigating main security flaws in web applications. We\'ll be using an active and cooperative learning method with online discussions and problem-based, hands-on project assignments.  If you run into challenges, reach out to your peers to discuss trouble-shooting options.  This will help drive your discovery and learning process.</string>
    <string name="description_587">This is a three (3) credit course spanning seven weeks that discusses software systems architecture, architectural design principles and patterns, documentation and evaluation of software architectures, and reuse of architectural assets through frameworks and software product lines.</string>
</resources>